MUHAMMAD ISMAIL

+6289687601023 | muhaisim7@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/muhismail015 | github.com/muhismail015 | Portfolio: muhismail.me | Kabupaten Bogor, Jawa Barat

INTRODUCTION

I am a Full-stack Web Developer who graduated in Information Technology from Sekolah Tinggi Teknologi Terpadu Nurul Fikri. With experience working on projects through Independent Study in the Kampus Merdeka program, volunteering, and collaborative projects. As an adaptable learner, I have successfully tackled various problem-solving challenges both individually and as part of a team. Im motivated to continue growing and contributing.

EXPERIENCE

PT. Kinema Systrans Multimedia | (Independent Study from Kampus Merdeka)

(Agu 2023 - Dec 2023)

Full-stack Web Developer

- · Design website pages using Figma.
- Implement design and create website using ReactJS Vite.
- · Design databases and build APIs using NodeJS and Express.js.
- Set up and deploying website using Virtual Machine from Google Cloud Platform.

PT. Nurul Fikri Cipta Inovasi | (Independent Study from Kampus Merdeka)

(Agu 2022 - Dec 2022)

Full-stack Web Developer

- · Collaborate project using Github.
- · Layouting template website content.
- Implement design and build APIs using Php Laravel.
- Deploy and hosting website that have been finished into Webmin.

Pemira STT-NF | (Volunteer)

(Jan 2022 - Mei 2022)

Full-stack Web Developer

- · Collaborate project using Github
- Design and create website pages for admin dashboard using Laravel.

EDUCATION

Sekolah Tinggi Teknologi Terpadu Nurul Fikri

(2020 - 2024)

Information Technology

Current GPA: 3.86

SMK Al-Hasra
Computer and Network Engineering

(2017 - 2020)

SKILLS

Programming Language: Php, Javascript. **Framework**: ReactJS Vite, Express.js, Laravel.

DBMS: MySQL/MariaDB.

DevOps: PM2, Linux Ubuntu, Apache2.

FEATURED PROJECTS

- SuikaBot A WhatsApp Bot with many usefull feature and integrated with AI using Google Gemini AI and Google Imagen.
- AuliaMotorManagement A website to manage inventory and financial data for Aulia Motor Workshop.
- Walntip A project to see one time view message from whatsapp, using whatsapp-web-js. Soon integrated in website version.

CERTIFICATIONS

- Web Development Infinite Learning (MSIB Batch 5), 02 January 2024
- Full-stack Web Developer Academy NF Computer (MSIB Batch 3), 31 December 2022
- Full-stack Web Development PKS Digital School (Bootcamp), 18 December 2021